(Leonard:)I'm kidding,
I want you to feel at home here.
(Leonard:)Decorate it any way
that makes you happy.
(Penny:)Do you really mean that?
(Leonard:)I really do.
(Penny:)Great, and just so you know,
(Penny:)I'm not getting rid
of all your stuff.
(Leonard:)Yeah? What are you keeping?
(Penny:)That candle
(Howard:)and you.
(Leonard:)What about my robot poster?
Buh, buh, buh, buh, buh.
(Penny:)I can make do
with just the candle.
(Amy:)What's going on?
(Sheldon:)I'm struggling with the thought
of leaving my old bedroom.
(Amy:)Can it be more
of an internal struggle?
(Sheldon:)I need to see it.
(Sheldon:)While I'm gone,
(Sheldon:)don't breathe on my pillow.
(Amy:)How about if I just don't
breathe at all?
(Sheldon:)That's my girl.
(Sheldon:)What on earth?